(Love In Sync)
(Kim Myung Soo)
(Kang Min Ah)
(Love In Sync)
(All people, incidents, and backgrounds...)
(in this drama are fictitious and unrelated to reality.)
(Also, children and animals were filmed under production guidelines.)
After Shin Mi Jeong exposed Ji An's bullying,
her mother passed away not long after.
- Her mother? - She was already battling cancer.
It seems her mother was her only family.
It's a shame, especially at her young age.
Anyway, she's been a recluse ever since.
There's no record of her whereabouts.
And her place of residence is unclear.
Really?
But who do you think you're talking to?
I went to the hospital where her mother was admitted,
and told them to contact me if Mi Jeong shows up.
So let's just wait.
They said her mother's things were still there.
She wouldn't just throw away her mom's keepsakes, right?
You're back?
Yes.
- Where's Ha Yul? - She's asleep.
Sorry, Song Hwan.
I haven't been much help lately, have I?
It's fine. It'll be over soon anyway.
Get some rest.
Oh, right.
You got some mail.
(Korea Psychological Counselling Association)
(Notice of Nullification of Disciplinary Action)
Is she cold?
What? Why are you glaring at me? Why?
I wasn't glaring.
Hey, I was just looking.
Then why were you looking at me?
It was creepy.
Jeez.
Here.
Is this your first winter shoot?
You should be prepared for things like this.
You were just as unprepared when you were an idol.
It's...
Sorry.
What?
I...
I said I'm sorry.
For what?
Just, you know...
For everything.
Are you sick or something?
You're unbelievable.
Anyway, I apologised.
Hello.
This is Mi Jeong, right?
Where are you right now?
This is the scene where your anger toward each other...
reaches its peak.
It's one of the most pivotal scenes in the story,
so I need you both to really focus.
- Yes. - But your chemistry is fantastic,
so I'm not worried about that, right?
All right. Let's take a short break, and then we'll start filming.
- Okay. - Okay.
Here.
Are you nervous?
Of course. It's the highlight of the movie.
And it's my first major scene with Yi Jin.
She's a great actress, you know.
It would be embarrassing if I'm the only one who bombs.
Are you feeling okay?
You seemed to have a cold this morning.
That's why I said you should go to the doctor.
What if I get drowsy from the medicine...
- right before a shoot? - You're a real pro now.
I was always a pro. It's just that no one noticed.
One moment.
Yes, Detective.
Yes.
Shin Mi Jeong?
Yes, I understand. I'll head over right now.
Okay, thank you.
What's so serious?
I heard that Shin Mi Jeong showed up at the hospital.
Mi Jeong?
I think I have to go right now.
Right now? But the shoot is about to start.
This is a really important scene.
Don't worry. It's not far from here.
I'll be back soon.
Even if I'm late, now...
you'll be able to do it on your own.
- What? - Believe in yourself.
(132 Ga 4819)
Why isn't he coming even now?
All right, let's start shooting. Everyone on standby.
You're always so cruel, Detective.
- What? - I've heard a lot about you.
And how you conduct your investigations.
Like a game...
I heard you treated your cases like a game.
You solve them, but you miss what's important.
And you did it again, didn't you?
You said I knew everything.
You said I was the mastermind of this game.
You're wrong.
Everything you assumed was wrong.
You...
You knew exactly what Lim Jun Ho did.
And you played all of us to cover for him.
Because I was arrogant enough to think I had figured out...
about you, the people I care about got hurt.
If you think you're the only one who's suffered through all this,
you're sorely mistaken.
That's why I'm going to solve this, no matter what.
Even if it means I have to take a completely different approach.
Cut, okay.
Are you awake?
You should have told me you had such a high fever.
Excuse me, the patient here...
Don't go.
I said don't go.
- Why are you calling? - Hey, I found him.
I found Kim Min Su.
(Scene 31, Hospital Hall, Night, Jeong Min Standing with a Phone)
He's overseas right now,
so he said he didn't know about Ji An's situation.
If you look at the original script he gave me,
the lines are identical to Ji An's bullying video.
He also said...
that he had the screen test footage for Ji An's part.
He said he'd send it over no matter how long it takes if we want.
He must have been secretly grateful to Ji An.
Well, he was an unknown director, but she didn't ignore him,
and agreed to be in his movie.
So, if we get the original script and the screen test footage,
won't that clear Ji An of the false bullying accusation right away?
And if we find out who was behind this,
it'll all be over.
(Detective)
Do Hoon, hold on.
This is Yi Jin's...
Why doesn't he ever listen?
Mr. Cha.
So I checked Shin Mi Jeong's bank records just in case,
and I found out a large sum of money was deposited...
right before the scandal broke.
The depositor was Han Yi Jin.
Why would Yi Jin send her so much money?
I think...
I think there's another culprit.
Is that really true?
Are you sure Yi Jin has been in contact...
with Shin Mi Jeong?
Well, I don't know if they're in contact,
but I saw her on the phone with her a few times.
On top of that, Yi Jin was the one...
who connected Ji An to that thug, CEO Noh.
If you think about it,
Yi Jin is a more likely suspect than the CEO, isn't she?
They've been enemies from the start.
- That's why the bullying video... - Is that really true?
Did Yi Jin really do that to me?
Ji An.
(Actress Han Yi Jin's Dressing Room)
We were in the middle of shooting a vlog.
Gosh, now there's even an assault on set.
I've been in this business for a long time,
but this is a first. What are you going to do now?
Hey, someone else did the hitting,
so why are you blaming the innocent Director Moon?
I was so against it, but he insisted on casting her.
He has to take responsibility.
How should I take responsibility?
Fire Yu Ji An.
Wait, if we fire Yu Ji An now,
what about the production costs for what we've already filmed?
That's not my problem.
How can the attacker and the victim act in the same space?
This is secondary victimization.
CEO Kim, please. Let's all calm down first.
CEO Kim does have a point.
I also feel that what happened on my set...
was deeply regrettable.
For now, let's suspend Yu Ji An's filming.
We'll figure out the next steps as we go.
Director Moon.
Come on, Director Moon, don't be too enraged.
Filming people to back them into a corner...
must be your hobby.
But what a shame.
I don't think you'll be able to enjoy...
that little hobby of yours anymore.
Because I'm going to make sure to block you.
Since there's no filming for a while anyway,
you don't have to come in starting tomorrow.
No, scratch that. Since it looks like...
I won't be able to make a comeback,
why don't we just terminate our contract?
That's what you wanted, right?
Then, goodbye.
I told you to leave. Why are you still standing there?
I said go. Go.
You were so desperate to leave.
- Ji An... - Just get out.
What did I do?
What did I do that was so wrong?
Why is everyone so eager to leave me?
People, CEO Kim,
Mi Jeong,
and Yi Jin.
Why?
You're just going to abandon me in the end anyway.
So...
just get out of here now.
When you're hurting like this,
how could I possibly leave?
So don't leave.
Don't abandon me, Cha Eun Hwan.
Please.
I told you, didn't I?
That I'd make sure you make a successful comeback.
Just trust me and wait a little longer.
And make sure you eat.
He's really terrible at cooking.
(Phone)
(Mom)
(My Daughter)
The party you are trying to reach is unavailable.
You will be connected to their voicemail...
(The Late Park Yoon Hee)
(Born: October 17, 1972, Died: January 24, 2026)
Who are you?
Ms. Shin Mi Jeong?
I came because I thought you might be here...
for your mother's memorial.
- I'm glad I found you. - Who are you?
I'm Yu Ji An's manager.
First, I'm very sorry for your loss.
You must have been through so much.
I know exactly why you're here, but it's no use.
I don't want to get involved in that case anymore.
Call me selfish and awful, but there's nothing I can do.
As for clearing Ji An of the bullying accusation,
I already have enough evidence to do that.
It's just that...
the reason I came to find you, Mi Jeong,
was in the hope of sparing Ji An some pain.
That's all.
Ji An...
Is she having a hard time?
Being betrayed by someone you trusted...
is a pretty terrible thing.
I'm not going to force you.
The choice is yours to make.
I'll be on my way, then.
Wait.
He said he'd introduce me to a doctor who could save my mom.
CEO Kim said that.
I didn't betray her for money.
I really didn't.
Darn it.
Filming people to back them into a corner...
must be your hobby.
I don't think you'll be able to enjoy...
that little hobby of yours anymore.
Fine.
The best defence is a good offence.
Hey, Manager Kim.
Get the reporters together right now.
Stop arguing and just do what I told you.
(J.An Entertainment)
The CEO is about to leave for a press conference right now.
I think he's planning...
to completely frame Ji An for assault.
Don't worry.
Soon, nobody will believe a word that guy says.
Fortunately, I'm only going to take down one guy.
So I'll give you a chance to save your own skin, Reporter Han.
This is the only piece of dirt I have on CEO Kim,
but you, Reporter Han...
I'm guessing it's a different story for you.
He needs to feel how gut-wrenching betrayal is...
for himself.
(J.An Entertainment)
Is everyone here? What about Yi Jin?
Darn it. She needs to be here...
and play the victim for this to be perfect.
Apparently, a lot more reporters showed up than we expected.
Really? I guess she still has pull.
Even after hitting rock bottom, Yu Ji An still has clout.
Let's go.
What is this? Hey, CEO Won, what is it?
I'm busy right now...
What?
Reporter Han? What's that bastard up to?
Hey. Hold on.
("Yu Ji An's Abuse of Power Controversy...")
("Was A Scheme by the CEO of J.An Entertainment")
Darn it.
(A Confession)
(Revealing the Truth Behind the Yu Ji An's Bullying Case)
No matter what I say, or for what reason,
I don't believe there are any excuses...
for what I've done.
I will humbly accept the consequences for my actions.
Is your head just for decoration? You should try thinking for once...
Am I being too calm to act like someone who's angry?
Is your head just for decoration?
You should try thinking for once...
Oh? Hey, perfect timing.
Again?
You know, having someone to act with versus not,
makes a difference getting in character.
Don't half-heartedly do it like before.
Act like you're really the one getting yelled at.
That's how I can immerse myself in the role.
Hey, where is your head at?
How many times do I have to tell you?
Is your head just for decoration? Do you even think at all?
You have no idea what's going on, do you?
Gosh. You're really driving me crazy.
What is all this mess just because of one bad hire?
Hey, I'm just asking because I'm genuinely curious,
do your parents know you go around acting like this?
Oh my, look at her. Are you crying?
Hey, why are you crying? I said, why are you crying?
Who do you think should be the one crying right now?
I told you not to cry. Stop crying.
Hey, wasn't my acting amazing?
Wasn't that just total method acting?
I know. You're really good at acting angry.
Who says you can't act? You're so good...
You act so good.
You got the angles right, didn't you?
- Bring it here so I can watch it. - Okay.
Lastly,
I want to say I'm sorry to Ji An,
who was always so genuinely kind to me.
Ji An.
I'm truly sorry.
I knew it. I believed in her all along.
She's amazing for enduring all that. All the best.
It's so sad to think of all the hate she got.
- Wish you all the best from now on. - I'm glad the truth is finally out.
She's a good actress too. Looks like she only has success ahead of her.
I told you, didn't I?
That you, Ji An, are absolutely...
not that kind of person.
So it really wasn't me.
I...
I was afraid that I might really be that kind of awful person.
Thank you.
For believing in me.
For revealing the truth.
If you're that grateful,
will you grant me a wish?
Is this really your wish? To spend the whole day with me?
Well, I never specified that it had to be you, Ji An.
Just like how other people hang out with their friends,
I said I wanted to spend just one day...
having fun without any worries.
Because I've never been able to do that.
Geez.
If you want to go on a date with me, just be honest and say it.
How many times do I have to tell you that you can't hide it?
Are you dumb?
I can hear everything, you know.
I can feel everything, you know.
Friends hold hands when they hang out these days.
Didn't you know?
It's okay.
It's...
- This or that? - That one.
Oh, they are cherry blossoms.
I've never been able to properly see...
the cherry blossoms because of filming.
Right now,
I'm about to do the most selfish thing in my life.
But just this once,
will you look the other way?
You're here.
- What are you doing here? - What do you mean?
Starting today, I'm your manager.
- What? - Didn't you hear anything...
from Mr. Cha?
He came to me himself and asked me to take good care of you.
- He said he's quitting. - He's quitting?
The phone is turned off. Connecting to voicemail. After the beep...
Where are you going?
Where's Eun Hwan?
- He's home, right? - He's not here.
- He left early this morning. - Left? Where to?
He didn't say anything to me.
I wouldn't know.
He left without telling me anything specific either.
But he must have had his reasons for leaving like that.
Reasons?
- What... - Since they can never be together,
wouldn't being together be more like a punishment for them?
Right now, I'm about to do the most selfish thing in my life.
Unable to connect. You will be forwarded to voicemail.
Ji An, the interview is starting soon.
He hasn't contacted you either, right?
Mr. Cha?
No.
Ever since he suddenly came to me and asked me to take care of you,
I haven't been able to contact him either.
You must have had a very difficult time...
with the abuse of power controversy.
Weren't you upset with the public for being so quick to judge?
I understand.
Even I...
found it hard to believe in myself.
I'm not sure.
He didn't really say anything to me before he left either.
You don't really expect me to believe that, do you?
There's no way he'd leave his sister and Ha Yul...
without asking you for help.
Tell me everything you know. Where is he now?
Why is he suddenly acting like this?
- Is he mad at me about something? - No.
It's not that.
Then what is it? Please, just tell me.
I don't really know either.
It just seems he has some things he needs to sort out.
Sort out what?
- Hello. - Hey, man.
Thanks to you, there's no way I'm getting into heaven.
How long do I have to play the bad guy?
Do you have any idea how Ji An is doing right now?
Is she having a hard time?
Of course she is.
The person she likes vanished into thin air.
How could she possibly be okay?
Man, she's a complete wreck. I was worried she'd collapse.
And you...
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
You're the one going through a hard time because of me.
Sorry.
He always says he's fine.
I must be crazy for even asking.
Hey, you too, man.
Don't suffer for too long before you come back.
I'll make you a meal.
I'm hanging up.
Unable to connect. You will be forwarded to voicemail.
What is the reason for all this?
Shouldn't you at least give me a reason?
Eun Hwan, were you always this selfish and irresponsible?
Forget it. From now on, wherever you are,
I don't care what you do.
So don't ever contact me again.
Your message has been saved.
Did you go on a trip somewhere?
It must be a really great place...
if you left without a word to me.
You should have taken me with you.
That's so cheap.
Can't you at least call me?
I'm so...
I'm so worried.
Cha Eun Hwan, you're...
You're such a jerk. A complete jerk.
Fine, have a great life all by yourself.
Just you wait until you get back.
I won't let you get away with this.
Next message.
When you come back,
I'll forgive you for everything.
So, please just come back.
I miss you so much.
No more messages.
(Dong Gyeong Kitchen)
Welcome.
Have you heard from him?
No.
Here's your order. Enjoy.
Still nothing?
Yes, well...
This is driving me crazy.
Yes, we're closed now.
Still...
You have soju here, right?
Soju?
You mean, not sparkling water?
Hey. Come on out, Cha Eun Hwan.
You jerk. You're in there, aren't you?
You selfish jerk.
You think I can't find you?
You jerk, I said come out. Come out.
You jerk.
Are you having fun toying with my heart?
I passed. I got the part.
One, two, three.
Friends hold hands when they hang out these days.
You shouldn't have been so nice to me.
You shouldn't have made me fall for you.
If you were just going to disappear like this,
what am I supposed to do?
Ladies and gentlemen,
our plane will be arriving...
at Incheon International Airport shortly.
Please be seated and ensure your seatbelts...
are securely fastened. Thank you.
Watch out.
Ji An.
Where are you right now? Ji An got hurt,
and she's asking for you.
(Regional Emergency Medical Center)
I'm here. Where should I go? How is Ji An...
I'm sorry. I had no other choice.
Your injuries...
Are you okay?
You jerk.
Did you have a nice trip?
You're not angry?
I can tell...
how sorry you are.
Then...
why did you do something you'd feel so sorry about?
Are you...
upset with me about something?
Or...
did I do something wrong?
No.
It's not that.
It's just that...
I've been having a hard time.
I mean, from my perspective,
helping you with your comeback,
playing manager, which I'm not cut out for,
and channelling your emotions...
Of course it wasn't going to be easy.
So you were cleared of the bullying accusation.
And since you started acting well without me,
I thought it was the right time to leave.
If that was too sudden,
I'm sorry about that.
All that time...
Was being with me...
that difficult for you?
I see.
But I enjoyed our time together.
So...
Did you enjoy your trip?
Where did you go?
The beach? The mountains?
Just...
a fishing spot.
A fishing spot?
It's a place I often went to with my father...
when I was a kid.
I suddenly felt the urge to go there.
That must have been nice.
So nice that you didn't even think of me.
You could have at least reached out.
- So I wouldn't have to worry. - What exactly are we?
I'm not your manager anymore.
We're not in any kind of relationship.
If a scandal breaks out because we're messaging each other...
You have to be careful after your difficult comeback.
Do you really think that?
That we're nothing to each other?
If we're nothing, then why are you here today?
When you hear that someone who means nothing to you got hurt,
do you always come running like a madman?
Even if it hadn't been you, Yu Ji An, I would've done the same.
So,
- don't read too much into it. - Then what was that kiss about?
Does a kiss really mean that much between us?
That kiss was...
just my way of saying goodbye.
Are we clear?
Then why can't you look me in the eye?
It's because you don't want me to see how you feel, isn't it?
- That's... - Do you know what the...
hardest part for me right now is?
The fact I know that every word you're saying...
is a lie.
I know it all.
And I can feel it all.
So why are you so desperate to push me away?
Why?
You really don't know why?
Someone who knows my every feeling.
Don't you think that would be terrifying for me?
I know you're lying.
(JJ Actors Entertainment)
(Cha Eun Hwan, Therapist, Tok Tok Mental Care)
(Observation: Ji An is exhibiting considerably open emotions.)
(CEO Kim)
(Controversial Therapy Method: "Imaginary Revenge" Psychotherapy)
(CEO Kim Jun Sik)
The party you are trying to reach is unavailable.
You will be connected to their voicemail...
She's ignoring my calls?
Darn it.
What, does she expect me to take the fall for this alone?
CEO Kim.
What? What is it?
Two of the rookie actors we signed last month...
have filed a lawsuit to terminate their contracts.
Those pathetic little punks.
And...
(District Court)
Han Yi Jin, too.
What?
Han Yi Jin?
(Complaint)
(Plaintiff: Han Yi Jin, Defendant: CEO Kim Jun Sik)
(Suit to Confirm Exclusive Contract Termination)
(CEO Kim Jun Sik)
Darn it.
(For Sale)
All right, great. Let's do it.
Wait, you're really going to sign right now?
You should look at a few more places.
- The location isn't great. - But I have the skills.
So what's the worry?
Now that I hear you talk, I'm reminded...
of what a jerk you've always been.
(For Rent or Sale)
I want to start working as soon as possible.
It'll keep my mind off things.
What?
The forecast didn't say anything about rain today.
I can't breathe.
Just do exactly as I do, okay?
Breathe in. One, two.
Breathe out. Three, four.
I'm not your manager anymore.
We're not in any kind of relationship.
If a scandal breaks out because we're messaging each other...
(Mom)
(Tuesday, March 24)
Hello? Could you please open the door?
Hello? Is anybody there?
Please, open the door.
Ji An.
The shoot's cancelled because of the rain.
(Actress Yu Ji An's Dressing Room)
What the...
Is it broken?
Oh, man.
It's raining out. This is so annoying.
Ji An, are you in there?
Ji An, are you okay?
Ji An.
Pick up.
Yes, is this maintenance? The door here is broken.
Please send someone quickly.
Right now.
Ji An is in there, and she is claustrophobic.
Help me.
Kiddo, if you don't want to do this, you can just say so.
No one will be mad at you.
You'll be all by yourself in this warehouse set.
Aren't you scared?
No. I'm not scared.
If at any point you get scared or feel like you're in danger,
just scream for help.
And I'll come running like Superman to save you.
- Got it? - Okay.
Okay.
Kiddo, stay with me.
Kiddo.
Are you okay?
Help me.
Okay. I'll definitely save you.
Don't lose consciousness, okay?